sailboatlistings.com 2017-12-21

# Sailboat Listings privacy policy

******What information do we collect?**

  * We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a contact form.
  * When registering on our site you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. 
  * When posting your boat for sale, you will be asked to enter contact information including your name, e-mail address, address, and phone number.
  * When contacting the seller of a boat, you will be asked for your name, phone number, and e-mail address so the seller may recieve and reply to your inquiry.
  * You may, however, visit and browse our site anonymously. 
  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to the website.
  * Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). 
  * Alternatively, users may opt out of third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

> **What do we use your information for?**

> Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To allow you to post your boat for sale and present sufficnt information to potential buyers or interested parties for them to contact you regarding the ad you place.
  * To transmit the contact information you provide when contacting the person who has posted a particular boat for sale to that seller so that you may communicate with him or her and so that he or she can communicate directly with you regarding the ad.
  * To personalize your experience
  * To send periodic emails regarding your ad. The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your ad. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you may login using the username and password you created your ad with and remove your ad from the site. 

> **How do we protect your information?**

> We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

**Do we use cookies?**

> Yes.
> 
> Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web Browser (if you allow in your browser settings) that enable the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 
> 
> We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to SailboatListings.com and other sites on the Internet. 
> 
> Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). 
> 
> You may also opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)

**Cookie Policy**

> In order to deliver the website while providing an optimal experience, cookies are required. By using our site, you consent to the use of cookies. You may disable cookies in your own web browser or device if you do not wish cookies to be used or stored, but your experience may be less than optimal due to untargeted ads and some functions may not work.

**Terms and Conditions**

> Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [www.sailboatlistings.com/terms-of-use/](http://www.sailboatlistings.com/terms-of-use/)

**Your Consent**

> By using our site, you consent to our website's privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

> If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**

> If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at [www.sailboatlistings.com/supportcenter/](https://www.sailboatlistings.com/supportcenter/)
